<page>
    <title>Documentation</title>
    <body>
        <![CDATA[
            <h2>Documentation</h2>
            <section>
                <h3>Documentation</h3>
                <h4>System requirements</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Windows 10</li>
                    <li>…that's all!</li>
                </ul>
                <h4>Browser support</h4>
                <ul>
                    <li>Edge (all versions)</li>
                    <li>Chrome (version 29 or later)</li>
                    <li>Firefox (version 28 or later)</li>
                    <li>Internet Explorer (version 11 or later)</li>
                </ul>
                <h4>Configuration</h4>
                <p>Configuration file is placed in config/config.xml. If you want to change the way the page looks or behaves by default, you need to edit that file.</p>
                <p>Neither the file nor any of the variables in it listed below are required for the UWP web framework to work properly.</p>
                <h5>Available config attributes:</h5>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>pageTitle</strong> <em>(string)</em> - specifies page title.</li>
                    <li><strong>layoutType</strong> <em>([tabs, pane-overlay, pane-semidocked, pane-docked], default: pane-overlay)</em> - specifies header type. See "Available layout types" for more information.</li>
                <h5>Available layout typesd</h5>
                <h4>Navigation</h4>
                <p>Navigations are created by creating an XML files in nav folder. default.xml is used by default. If you want to amend main menu items, you need to edit that file.</p>
                <p>There are several navigation areas that you can amend using that file.</p>
                <h5>Available navigation areas:</h5>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>mainMenu</strong> - main menu.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Each navigation area might consist of several navigation lists. Each navigation area will treat them a little differently to match UWP design guidelines.</p>
                <h5>Default navigation areas behavior:</h5>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>mainMenu</strong> - If you use layoutType pane-*: All the lists but the last one will be separated from the others with a line. The last list is fixed to the bottom of the navigation pane. If you use layoutType tabs: All the list but the first one will be hidden.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Each navigation list might consist of several elements.</p>
                <h5>Available navigation list elements attributes:</h5>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>label</strong> <em>(string)</em> - required - a text label that will be visible on the list.</li>
                    <li><strong>icon</strong> <em>(string or HTML entity)</em> - an icon that will be visible on the list.</li>
                    <li><strong>target</strong> <em>(string)</em> - required - an ID of the page that should be opened by the navigation element.</li>
                </ul>
                <h4>Pages</h4>
                <p>Pages are created by creating an XML file in pages folder. If you want to create a page with page ID "potato", you need to create pages/potato.xml file.</p>
                <p>The ID specified can be used later by linking to it in navigation or by creating a link in any other page.</p>
                <h5>Available page attributes:</h5>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>title</strong> <em>(string)</em> - required - page title.</li>
                    <li><strong>nav</strong> <em>(string, default: default)</em> - navigation used by the page.</li>
                    <li><strong>body</strong> <em>(CDATA)</em> - required - page body.</li>
                </ul>
            </section>
        ]]>
    </body>
</page>